omnicoreagency.com 2019-12-15

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

The mere act of visiting the website, even without reading the subject legal document, will be viewed as acceptance of the terms contained in that document, as modified from time to time by us. Please read it carefully.

## What Information do we collect During Your Visit?

Omnicore Agency utilizes Google Analytics and other Analytics tools to track visitors activity for better user experience. Omnicore Agency has enabled Google Analytics features such as: including features such as display advertising, remarketing, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest reporting. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads). Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting our [Cookies opt-out policy page](https://www.omnicoreagency.com/browser-cookies-settings) for all browsers with complete instructions.

## How Cookies Work

A “cookie” is a small text file that a web site can place on your computer’s hard drive in order, for example, to collect technical information about your activities on the site e.g. make it possible for you to use an online “shopping cart” to keep track of items you wish to purchase. The “cookie” transmits this information back to the web site’s computer that, generally speaking, is the only computer that can read it. You may set your web browser to warn you whenever a site attempts to place a cookie on your computer or refuse to accept cookies. Omnicore Agency will use cookies collected during your visit to this site for the purpose of facilitating your use of our site and for maintaining statistics concerning use of our site that will help us make improvements. The other purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page, so that when you visit the site again, the experience will be personalized. Technical information collected by cookies will not be linked to your personal information. We do not have access to your computer or any other information about you through the use of cookies. Third party vendors, including Google, use first-party and third-party cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to Omnicore Agency’s website. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

##  The Type of Information the Website Collects

 **a).** We request information from the customer on all forms on our website. For instance, when you fill out a form, complete a survey, make a purchase, subscribe to any of our publications, register for certain services, or register and/or set up an account to access certain portions of the Website, or the Website as a whole, you may provide a credit, debit, or charge card number, or other payment information such as your name, telephone number, email, street address, age, gender, mobile phone number, and other personally identifiable information. You may also provide information about your company such as your position/title, customer demographics, budget preferences, size of company, and other information regarding your job and company so we can better cater to your needs. All such information shall be referred to in this Privacy Policy as your “Registration Information”. **b.)**  Our servers may also automatically collect information about you, your online behavior and the device from which you access the Website. The information collected may include the make, model, settings, specifications, and geographic location of your device, as well as clickstream data related to your online behavior. This information is primarily used to provide insight into our audience’s preferences and how we can best cater to these preferences.

## How the Website Uses and Shares Information About You

 **a.)** Omnicore Agency uses the information we collect from all of our web pages to provide, maintain, protect and improve the content on our sites as well as the services we offer. Unless you consent, Omnicore Agency will use your personal information for the purpose for which it was submitted such as to reply to inquiries, handle your business requests related to program participation, and we will use such information to provide operational notices, and in program record keeping and to conduct research on industry marketplace practices. Our research may lead to the publication of aggregate demographic data but will not result in the reporting or publication of any personal information provided to us. **b.)** If you choose to purchase products and/or services, including without limitation proprietary online marketing tools and/or content, on or through features on the Website, we may forward your information to third parties for services such as credit card or other payment processing, order fulfillment, credit pre-authorization, and address verification. Some of the information you have provided about yourself may be managed by third parties. In such cases, the information may be used by such third parties, each pursuant to its own policies. While we will only authorize them to use this information for the express purpose for which it is provided, we do not bear any responsibility for inappropriate use by these third parties.

## Help Us Keep Your Personal Information Accurate

If your personal information changes or you would like to review the personal information we may have on file, please email us with the new information or your review request at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#264f48404966494b484f4549544347414348455f0845494b)

## Transfer of Information

Please be advised that your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, servers and databases located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as your jurisdiction. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to any such transfer.

## Links to other Websites

Omnicore Agency site may contain links to other websites whose privacy policy may differ. If you submit any information to these sites, we encourage you to carefully review their privacy policy to understand how they will handle your personal information.

## Notification of Changes and Security

Because no data transmission is completely secure, we cannot guarantee the security of the information you send to us or the security of our servers, networks or databases, and by using the Website you agree to assume all risk connected to the information collected by us when you access, visit and/or use the Website, including the personally identifiable information or other Registration Information you have provided through the Website, and that we are not responsible for any loss of such information or the consequences thereof.

## Email Address

Omnicore Agency may use your e-mail address and other personal information included in your correspondence to improve the content of our web site or to respond to your correspondence. Omnicore Agency also uses this information to offer you tailored content as well as information about us, about our products and services, and about special offers such as sweepstakes or other promotions. You are automatically subscribed to any and all promotional emails and newsletters. You may choose to unsubscribe from these notifications by following the instructions and/or opt-out links provided in the mailings themselves.

## Blogs

Any personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data that you disclose through the blogs hosted on the website, may be collected and used by others. Omnicore Agency is not responsible for the privacy policies or other content on third‐party websites accessed through Omnicore Agency’s website. Omnicore blog is _NOT_ for Customer Feedback relevant to Omnicore services.

## Social Sharing Cookies

On our blog, we use social sharing buttons for services including, but not limited to, Twitter, LinkedIn, Share This, Google+ and Facebook. These allow you to share pages with your friends via those networks. Whilst you will be asked to login to use these services, this process is handled directly with the social sharing providers and their databases and servers. These sites may also monitor your usage of these buttons, through the use of external tracking codes that are required to run the buttons on this website.

## Children’s Online Privacy Protection

In accordance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not knowingly collect any personal information from anyone under 13 years of age. There is no plausible way for us to enforce an age restriction on users. However, we will take all reasonable measures necessary to remove such information from our databases and not use such information for any purpose except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others or as required by law.

## Legal

We reserve the right to access, use, and share with others your personally identifiable information without notice for only if required to do so by law or in good faith belief that such an action is necessary to **a.)**  We believe in good faith that it is necessary to comply with subpoenas, court orders and other legal process as required or permitted by law. **b.)** for the act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Omnicore Agency, its websites, or the public. **c.)** protect and defend the rights or property of Omnicore Agency or one of Omnicore Agency’s websites; and, **d.)** To report, prevent or assist in the investigation of suspected fraud or other illegal activities or take actions associated with such activities. **e.)** To enforce the Omnicore Agency Terms of Services, establish, exercise or defend our legal rights or as otherwise provided in the Terms and Conditions.

## Notification of Changes

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change, modify or revise this Privacy Statement, the Site or our services simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Site. Any such addition, update, change, modification or revision will be effective immediately upon posting, therefore, this document should be regularly referred to for updates and variations.

## Refund Policy

All payments made for services are final as agreed upon in the client contract form. Payments are only requested when the client agrees on the project deliverables and the scope of work which means Omnicore reserves the right to keep any funds that have been paid for the consultation and services we offer.

##  **Amazon Affiliate Program Disclaimer**

OmnicoreAgency.com participates in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, which is a way for OmnicoreAgency.com to earn revenue by advertising and linking products from amazon.com and any of its affiliated websites, including but not limited to any other sites affiliated with the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program.

 **Amazon Trademark Disclaimer:**

All Amazon markings and logos are the exclusive trademarks and property of Amazon.com, Inc. or its affiliates or subsidiaries.

## How to Contact Us:

Omnicore Agency welcomes feedback regarding this Policy. If you have any questions or concerns about the scope, provisions or application of this policy please contact Omnicore Agency and we will use all commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and correct the problem. Omnicore Agency,

London, United Kingdom +44 (208) 133-8513  info [at] omnicoreagency.com
